

CONTACTS

Email: dog.vol.serg@gmail.com

Telegram: @sergak0 Github: @sergak0 Phone: +79166260384

ABOUT

In high school, I studied algorithms and data structures a lot and even won several All-Russian and one international Olympiad in Informatics. For the last two years I have been engaged in machine learning and neural networks. Currently I am studying at the Higher School of Economics (HSE) in the program of applied Mathematics and Computer Science.

English proficiency: C1 Advanced (IELTS 6.5)

ACHIEVEMENTS

- 2nd place at the all-Russian Machine Learning Championship | 2022
- <u>1st place</u> on the Digital Breakthrough (Northwest Federal District) | 2022
- 1st place at the Tochka bank hackathon | 2022
- <u>7th place</u> at the hand-writing text recognition competition | 2022
- Prize-winner at Russian Olympiad in Informatics | 2021, 2022 year
- Bronze medal at International Zhautykov Olympiad in Computer Science | 2021

CONFERENCES

- Judge at <u>"Start in Innovation"</u> Conference | May 2022
- Speaker at <u>EdCrunch</u> International Conference (the world's biggest conference in education).
 Made a speech about Fora. Vision and digital technologies for physical education in schools and universities | Nov. 2022

SERGEY VOLNOV

ML/DL Engineer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data Scientist, Tochka bank | July 2022 - Now

- Developing a model for customer churn rate prediction (looking for those who would go to another bank) at Tochka.
- The revenue for the bank from this model was about \$20000/quarter.
- Used technlogies: Machine Learning, Time-series, SQL, Boostings, a/b tests

DL Engineer, Freelance | May 2022 - June 2022

- Developing a system for furniture detection and removal in 3D room scan with subsequent holes repainting.
- Used technologies: Deep Learning, Graph Networks, PyTorch, 3D instance segmentation, Repainting (LAMA), Color mesh optimization, Clusterings.

PROJECTS

DL Engineer & Founder at <u>Fora.Vision</u> | August 2021 - Now

- Online training service with computer vision technologies and real-time recognition of completed exercises.
- Now we have several educational organizations among our clients (ITMO, Phystech-Lyceum, etc.) and more than 300 constantly training students
- Used technologies: Deep Learning, Computer Vision, PyTorch, ONNX, Docker, Fastapi, Websocket, Asyncio

Face cartoonizing | Nov. 2021 - Dec. 2021

- Telegram bot for generation cartoonized image from faces
- Used technologies: Deep Learning, PyTorch, GAN-based pix2pix models, Face object detection, ONNX, Docker, Telebot, Asyncio

EDUCATION

- Faculty of Computer Science in HSE | 2022-Now
- <u>Deep Learning School</u> (advanced flow) Deep Learning (PyTorch) | 2021-2022
- Tinkoff ML Machine Learning | 2021-2022
- <u>Tinkoff Generation</u> (levels B', B and A) Algorithms and Structures of Data | 2019-2022
- Academy of Artificial Intelligence- Deep Learning (Keras) | 2020-2021

SKILLS

- Languages: Python, C++
- Tehnologies: Docker, Bash, Git, Jira
- Data Bases: SQL, PostgreSQL
- Knowledge: Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Algorithms and Structures of Data, A/B tests, Production Deploy